https://docs.hasbro.com/en-us/legal/privacy#right-to-opt

HASBRO WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY (Privacy Policy PDF)(Last Updated: 11/13/2020)  WELCOME!This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how Hasbro, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies that operate within the United States (collectively, "Hasbro", “we”, “our”, or “us”) collect, use and disclose your information when you visit our websites. This Policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites and other online products and services where this Policy is posted (collectively, the "Services") or interact with us offline regarding the Services.This Policy and the ESRB certification seals shown on our Services confirm that Hasbro is a valid licensee, and participating member, of the Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Certified Program (“ESRB Privacy Certified”). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and have had all of our Services where this Policy is posted reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Certified to meet established online information collection, use and disclosure practices. As a licensee of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our Services and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. If you are a California resident, please see the “Additional disclosures for California residents” section below. We ask that you take the time to read this Policy carefully. By using our Services, you agree to this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Services. Table of Contents1.      Changes to this Policy2.      What information is collected from me?3.      How does Hasbro use my information?4.      How does Hasbro handle children’s information?5.      With whom does Hasbro share my personal information?6.      What are my information choices?7.      Security8.      Additional disclosures for California residents9.      Contact Us 1. Changes to this PolicyWe encourage you to review this Policy whenever you access the Services to make sure that you understand our information collection, use and disclosure practices. We may change the provisions of this Policy at any time and will indicate when changes have been made by revising the date at the top of this Policy. Your use of the Services, or any portion thereof, following the posting of such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will provide you with additional notice of such changes by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us, or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the applicable website(s). If you do not agree with the changes we make to this Policy, please stop using the Services.Back to top2. What information is collected from me?Information That You ProvideHasbro may collect information that you provide when you use the Services, such as when you:(1) send questions or comments via email or live chat to Hasbro customer support;(2) fill out online surveys;(3) sign up for our newsletter or other email alerts;(4) share a website with a friend;(5) share a news release through our investor website;(6) provide information necessary to obtain parental consent; or(7) otherwise communicate with us through the Services.Depending on the activity, the types of personal information that you and we or our service providers collect, including in the last 12 months, may include:(1) your first and/or last name;(2) email address(3) telephone number;(4) address (including billing address and/or shipping address); and(5) other contact or identifying information that you choose to provide.Non-personal information you may also provide includes your birth date, gender, toy and game ownership and preferences, company name, and job title. When you provide this information at the same time as you provide certain personal information (e.g., your name or other contact or identifying information), we may combine these data points. Standing alone, these pieces of non-personal information we collect cannot be used to identify or directly contact you. However, when we combine your non-personal information with your personal information, it may become personally identifiable (e.g., first and last name combined with birth date).In some cases, we may also collect information you provide about others, such as when you refer someone to our Services (including promotions). We will use this information to fulfill your requests and will not send communications to your contacts unrelated to your requests, unless they separately consent to receive communications from us.Please note that this Policy applies to any information we collect when you use our Services or offline.Information We Collect Automatically From You.When you access or use our Services, we may also automatically collect information about your visit. When you visit our websites, the personal information we collect is your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, which we use for the support of our internal operations. The non-personal information we and our service providers may collect includes your operating system, access times, browser type and language, country, and the URL of the website you visited before navigating to our Services. If you access our Services via a mobile device, we may also collect your device make and model, mobile carrier, operating system version, language your device is set to, mobile web browser type and version, the country in which you are using your device, and non-personal analytics and statistical data regarding use of the websites (e.g., downloads, number of users, sessions, frequency of use, retention, territories, and in-game events). Please be sure to review Hasbro’s Mobile Privacy Policy to learn more about our privacy practices in relation to mobile application usage.To collect this information, we use various technologies, including the following:Cookies: Cookies are small data files stored on your computer or mobile device by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits. In addition, when you view a video on our Services, we may set a "flash cookie" (sometimes called a "flash object") on your computer or device. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "What are my information choices?" below.Clear GIFs: Clear GIFs, sometimes called "web bugs" or "web beacons," are small electronic images that are placed on a web page or in an email message. We use clear GIFs to monitor user behavior, deliver cookies, collect information, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, and to tell if a recipient has opened and acted upon an email.Log Files: Log files record website activity on our Services and enable us to gather statistics about our users' browsing habits. These entries help Hasbro determine (among other things) how many and how often users have accessed or used our Services, which pages of our Services they've visited, and other similar data.Do Not Track (DNT) Signals: Your browser may allow you to set a Do Not Track (DNT) signal indicating that you do not wish your online activity to be tracked. Currently, our system does not support and cannot act on DNT signal headers that we may receive. However, the choices that we provide you concerning collection and use of your personal information will continue to operate as described in this Privacy PolicyWe may associate the information we collect from these technologies with other personal information that you provide for the purposes described in this Policy.Information We Collect from Other Sources We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a third-party social networking site, we may have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and friends, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such third-party social networking site.Third-Party TechnologyFor a list of third-party partners whose technology we have integrated on our site, please click here. If you have any inquiries regarding our partner's privacy practices or how they use your information, you can review our partner’s privacy policy and terms of use or contact Hasbro Consumer Care.Website AnalyticsWe use analytics services and software provided by third parties (identified here) to help us understand how users access and use the Services. These tools and services use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies on our Services to enable them to track traffic data. The data collected typically includes information such as your IP address, your Internet Service Provider, your web browser, the time spent on web pages, the links clicked and the advertisements viewed on those pages. We use this information to improve our Services and your experience, to see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and to count visits.Third Party AdvertisingWe engage third parties to place ads for our products and services on other websites. These third parties use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies to collect information about your visits to websites and mobile applications, including Hasbro’s websites and mobile applications. The data collected typically includes information such as your IP address, your web browser, web pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and whether you purchased an advertised product. These third parties use this information to deliver advertising and/or content targeted to your interests. For more information about targeted advertising provided by these third parties, and how to opt out of having your information used in this way by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance, please visit: www.aboutads.info/choices or www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. You may refer to our list of third parties ( here) in order to see which of our third party service providers offer consumer opt-out choices through the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) and/or Network Advertising Initiative’s (NAI) sites. Hasbro is not responsible for the effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third parties’ opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their opt-out options or programs.Back to top3. How does Hasbro use my information?Use of InformationWe use personal information collected through our Services for the purposes described in this Policy or as otherwise disclosed to you on or in connection with our Services. For example, we may use your information to:Send you advertising or promotional materials, including information about new products, contests, features and enhancements, special offers and other events of interest from Hasbro and our select partners;Operate and improve our Services, including by linking or combining your information with other information we get from third parties;Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;Respond to your comments, questions, and requests and provide customer service;Monitor performance of the Services, overall usage of the Services and user retention rates, track how users are engaging in the games, identify which website features are least and most utilized, identify problem areas within the websites, and inform design development for future application updates; andCarry out any other purpose conveyed to you at the time the information was collected.Back to top4. How does Hasbro handle children’s information?NOTE TO PARENTSHasbro has developed its Services to be an enjoyable experience for users of all ages, including those under 13 (“Children” or “Child”). Please discuss this Policy with your Children so that they will better understand how to use the Services and the information they may be asked to provide when using the Services. Hasbro believes that providing its visitors with accurate and adequate notice about the Services will inform choices and decisions about how to use the Services and will better protect its users' privacy. If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us using the contact information provided at the end of this section.Hasbro is committed to compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), a federal law designed to protect Children online. We take Children's privacy seriously and encourage parents to take an active role in protecting their Children's privacy and online experience at all times. Except as otherwise outlined in this Policy, we do not collect personal information from users of the Services.Services Directed to ChildrenHasbro’s Services contain content appropriate for a wide range of audiences, including Children. For a list of Services that Hasbro treats as being directed to Children under COPPA, please contact hopp.us@hasbro.com.Collection and Use of Children's Personal InformationHasbro may collect and store persistent identifiers (e.g., cookies, IP addresses, etc.) from Children without parental consent for the purpose of supporting the internal operations of the Service or as otherwise permitted under COPPA.Hasbro may collect and store other personal information about Children if this information is submitted by a Child with prior parental consent or by the parent or guardian of the Child. If a Service is directed to children under COPPA, we may ask users to verify their dates of birth before collecting any personal information from them. Those users that indicate they are Children are either blocked from the activity or taken through a parental consent process.Hasbro may collect and store the following types of personal information about a Child when submitted by a Child with prior parental consent or by the parent or guardian of the Child: first and/or last name, email address, parent's or guardian's name, and parent's or guardian's email address. Hasbro may also collect the Child's mailing address and/or telephone number when necessary to respond to an inquiry or fulfill a transaction, such as sending the winner of a contest or sweepstakes the awarded prize. Hasbro may also collect demographic information about a Child such as the Child's date of birth, gender, toy and game ownership and other preferences, and combine such information with the Child's personal information. Please refer to the sections entitled "What information is collected from me?" and “How does Hasbro use my information?” for further details on the information we collect and the tools we use to collect it.When registering an account to play online games, we may collect a username and password from registrants for the purpose of saving that user’s gaming activities (e.g., pets collected in Littlest Pet Shop). Once collected, we may also use the game play information for our internal marketing and demographic studies so that we can improve the products and services we provide our visitors in order to better meet their needs, or as otherwise described in this Policy. Please note that we use aggregated (i.e., non-personal) information for analytics purposes.Additionally, we are prohibited by COPPA from conditioning a Child's participation in an activity - like contests - on the Child's disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. This means that if we don't need a specific piece of information (like the Child's phone number) to allow the Child to participate in a contest, we simply won't ask for it, even with parental consent. To read about the steps Hasbro takes to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of all users’ personal information, please see our section on "Security".Disclosure of Children's Personal InformationWe follow our standard policy ("With whom does Hasbro share my personal information?") for the disclosure of personal information collected from and about Children.Parental AccessA parent who has already given Hasbro permission to collect and use his or her Child's personal information can, at any time, do the following: (1) review, correct, or delete the Child's personal information; and/or (2) discontinue further collection or use of the Child's personal information. To do so, please refer to the confirmation email provided to you when you gave consent or contact Hasbro Consumer Care. Please be sure to include your Child's name and email address, your name and email address, and the name of the site on which your Child is registered. Alternatively, you may contact us at:Hasbro, Inc.Attention: Website Administrator1027 Newport Avenue, Mailstop A906Pawtucket, RI 02861(800) 255-5516For any other issue, please contact Hasbro Consumer Care. We will be happy to take your request.Back to top5. With whom does Hasbro share my personal information?Sharing of InformationWe do not share your personal information with third parties other than as described in this Policy or in connection with the Services, including:With your consent, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;With third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us. We require these entities to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us.With our affiliates for internal business purposes;Except for information collected from Children, with our affiliates and third parties for Hasbro’s own marketing purposes and those affiliates’ and third parties’ own business purposes, including direct marketing purposes (California residents have certain rights set forth in the section entitled  “Additional Disclosures for California Residents”);When we believe it is necessary or appropriate to: (i) comply with applicable law or legal process or to respond to lawful requests or legal authorities; (ii) protect the rights and property of Hasbro and our employees, agents, users and other third parties, including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use and protect against fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate, or unlawful use of our Services; and (iii) protect the safety of Hasbro, our users or any third party; andIn connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, bankruptcy or reorganization, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.We may also share aggregated information or information that we have collected from you through the Services, including on co-branded pages and where we have taken reasonable measures to de-identify such information.Social Sharing FeaturesThe Services may offer third party social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook widget), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features may enable the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides these features. The third party provider may also collect other information in connection with your use of their features, including your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Services, and may set a cookie to enable the features to function properly. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.Linking to Third Party SitesTo provide relevant information not found on our Services, to facilitate online shopping, and to allow you to interact with other websites and/or applications in which you may have accounts (such as Facebook and other social media sites), Hasbro may provide links to or embed third-party applications that allow login from our Services to third party websites. Your use of these third party websites and/or applications is subject to the third parties' privacy policies and terms of use, and we encourage you to read the third parties' privacy policies and terms of use before submitting personal or other information or using the websites and/or applications.Matched List AdsThird party websites and applications may display ads from Hasbro that are targeted to reach people on those websites or applications who are also identified on one or more of Hasbro’s databases. This is done by matching common factors between Hasbro’s databases - except for information collected from Children - and the databases of these third parties. For instance, we may share your email address with Facebook as part of Facebook’s matched list ad services. If we use Facebook’s matched list ad services, you should be able to opt-out of such services on Facebook by, for example, hovering over the box in the right corner of the Facebook ad to find out how to opt-out from such list. If you opt-out from Facebook matched list ad services, Facebook will process your opt-out request on the Facebook platform; however, this will not take effect immediately and if you have multiple emails or other accounts, you may have to opt-out separately for each one. We are not responsible for Facebook or other such third parties’ failure to comply with your or our opt-out instructions.Back to top6. What are my information choices?Regarding Personal InformationIf you have registered with our Services, you may at any time review and/or update the contact information we have for you or inform us that you want us to remove your information from our database by either visiting the online profile section of one of our Services or contacting Hasbro Consumer Care. If you choose to send us an email, please be sure to include in your message, the name of the website at which you registered and the email address you used to register so that we can verify your request. We will respond to all access requests as soon as possible.Regarding CookiesMost web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.Regarding Promotional CommunicationsYou may opt out of receiving promotional emails, text messages or mail from Hasbro by declining to receive such communications at the time of registration or at the time you otherwise provide the information to us. You may also opt-out of receiving promotional emails or text messages by following the instructions in those emails or text messages or by sending an email to Hasbro Consumer Care. If you opt out, we may still send you transactional or relationship messages, such as emails about your account or our ongoing business relations.Back to top7. SecurityHasbro has established policies in an effort to protect your personal information against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and/or destruction. For example, Hasbro strives to provide only those employees performing a legitimate business function with access to users’ personal information. Hasbro also reviews its security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods.Hasbro retains your information for business purposes, for as long as your account is active, and/or as long as is reasonably necessary to provide you with our products and services. Hasbro will also retain your information as reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. We may also retain cached or archived copies of your information for a reasonable period of time.Despite our efforts, please be aware that no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable. To that end, Hasbro will notify users of a data breach when Hasbro determines that is reasonably necessary in accordance with applicable law.Back to top8. Additional Disclosures for California ResidentsThese additional disclosures for California residents apply only to individuals who reside in California. The California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) provides additional rights to know, delete and opt out, and requires businesses collecting or disclosing personal information to provide notices and means to exercise rights.CALIFORNIA NOTICE OF COLLECTIONIn the past 12 months, we or our service providers have collected the following categories of personal information enumerated in the CCPA in connection with the Services:Identifiers, including IP address.Name, address, phone number, and mailing address to the extent you are interacting with our Consumer Care site.Internet activity, including history of visiting and interacting with our Services, browser type, browser language and other information collected automatically.Geolocation data, including location enabled services such as WiFi.For more information on information we collect, including the sources we receive information from, review the "What information is collected from me?" section. We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes described in the “How does Hasbro Use My Information” section, including to provide, manage and improve our Services. Hasbro does not generally sell information as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. However, to the extent “sale” under the CCPA would be interpreted to include any of the activities described in the "With whom does Hasbro share my personal information?" section, we will comply with applicable law as to such activity.RIGHT TO KNOW AND DELETEIf you are a California resident, you have the right to delete personal information we have collected about you and you have the right to know certain information about our data practices in the preceding 12 months. In particular, you have the right to request the:categories of personal information we have collected about you;categories of sources from which the personal information was collected;categories of personal information about you we disclosed for a business purpose or sold;categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or disclosed for a business purpose;business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the personal information; andspecific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request to us by calling our toll-free number at (800) 255-5516, or by completing the request form found here. In the request, please specify which right you are seeking to exercise and the scope of the request. We will confirm receipt of your request within 10 days. We may require specific information from you to help us verify your identity and process your request. Please note that, in many instances, Hasbro does not collect types of personal information that enable us to identify you. As such, if we do not have information that permits us to verify your identity, we may deny your requests to know or delete.RIGHT TO OPT OUTUnder the California Consumer Privacy Act, you have the right to opt out of the sale of your personal information to third parties at any time. Hasbro does not “sell” your personal information as it is currently defined under the CCPA. You may contact us by calling our toll-free number at (800) 255-5516, or emailing us at DPO@hasbro.com if you have any questions or concerns.AUTHORIZED AGENTYou can designate an authorized agent to submit requests on your behalf. However, we will require written proof of the agent’s permission to do so and verify your identity directly.RIGHT TO NON_DISCRIMINATIONYou have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for the exercise of any your rights.SHINE THE LIGHTCalifornia Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of this website who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information as defined by the statute to our affiliates and third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please call or write us at:Hasbro, Inc.Attention: Website Administrator1027 Newport Avenue, Mailstop A906Pawtucket, RI 02861(800) 255-5516Back to top9. Contact UsIf you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact us using the following contact information:Hasbro, Inc.Attention: Website Administrator1027 Newport Avenue, Mailstop A906Pawtucket, RI 02861(800) 255-5516 For any other issues, please contact Hasbro Consumer Care. For additional information about our Services, please see our Terms and Conditions of Use.As aforementioned, Hasbro is a licensee of the ESRB’s Privacy Certified Program. If you believe that we have not responded to your privacy-related inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact ESRB at https://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.aspx or:ESRBprivacy@esrb.org
Please enter your birthday:
Month
01
02
03
04
05
06
07
Confirm
We’re sorry, but you are not eligible to access this site.
If you believe you received this message in error, please contact us for assistance.
OK
You are now leaving Hasbro.com
Hasbro does not control and is not responsible for the availability of, or content on, linked third party websites.
Please be aware that your use of such third party's linked website is subject to their privacy policy and terms of use, which may differ from those of Hasbro.
As such, we encourage you to read the third party's privacy policy and terms of use closely.
continue
go back
